<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root> 
    <fans mentioned="1"> "Fans,</fans> for the past two weeks you have been reading about the <sickness mentioned="1"> bad break</sickness> <lucky mentioned="1"> luckiest man </lucky> on the face of this earth. I have been in <baseball mentioned="1"> ballparks</baseball> for seventeen years and have never received anything but kindness and encouragement from you <fans mentioned="2">fans. </fans>
    
    "Look at these grand <men mentioned="men"> men</men>. Which of you wouldn't consider it the highlight of his career just to associate with them for even one day? Sure, I'm <lucky mentioned="2"> lucky </lucky>. Who wouldn't consider it an honor to have known <men mentioned="JacobRuppert"> Jacob Ruppert</men>? Also, the builder of <baseball mentioned="2">> baseball's </baseball> greatest empire,<men mentioned="EdBarrow"> Barrow </men>? To have spent six years with that wonderful little fellow,<men mentioned="MillerHuggins"> Miller Huggins</men>? Then to have spent the next nine years with that outstanding leader, that smart student of psychology, the best manager in baseball today, <men mentioned ="JoeMcCarthy"> Joe McCarthy</men>? Sure, I'm <lucky mentioned="3"> lucky.</lucky>
    
    "When the <team mentioned="NewYorkGiants"> New York Giants </team>, a team you would give your right arm to beat, and vice versa, sends you a gift - that's something. When everybody down to the <people mentioned="groundskeepers"> groundskeepers</people> and those <people mentioned="BoysInWhiteCoats"> boys in white coats</people> remember you with trophies - that's something. When you have a wonderful <family mentioned="MotherInLaw"> mother-in-law</family> who takes sides with you in squabbles with her own daughter - that's something. When you have a <family mentioned="father">father </family>and a <family mentioned="mother"> mother</family> who work all their lives so you can have an education and build your body - it's a blessing. When you have a <family mentioned="wife"> wife</family> who has been a tower of strength and shown more courage than you dreamed existed - that's the finest I know.
    
    "So I close in saying that I may have had a <sickness mentioned="2"> tough break </sickness>, but I have an awful lot to live for."</root>